Finding Aid for University of Michigan. Dept. of Medicine and Surgery Theses, 1851-1878
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Medical Theses
  - Class of 1877
    - Woodruff, Lettie Helen, "Notes on the History of Medicine", 1877 (Reel 57)
    - Wooldridge, Charles William, "The Physiology and Therapeutics of Light", 1877 (Reel 57)
  - Class of 1878
    - Lewitt, Adelaide, "Epileptic Puerperal Insanity", 1878 (Reel 57)
  - Undated
    - Donovan, D., "Dislocations", undated (Reel 57)
      [No record of Donovan's having attended UM medical school]